《尖峰时刻2》
（美国领事馆）
谢谢
Thank you.
还不叫警察去
∮ 我希望她们都是加州女孩 ∮
∮ I wish they all could be California girls ∮
- 《沙滩小子》太棒了 - 我真的很爱《沙滩小子》
- The Beach Boys are dope. - I love Beach Boys.
嘿 美女 你们好吗？
Hey, ladies, how you doing?
等等
Wait a minute.
你们去哪啊 我们去吃寿司吧
Hey, where you going? Let's get some sushi!
喂 喂 美女
Hey! Hey, cutie!
∮ 我希望她们都是… ∮
∮ I wish they all could… ∮
嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
那张CD是我的
That was my CD.
别碰中国人的CD
Don't you ever touch a Chinese man's CD.
看到她们开车离开的样子吗 她们在嘲笑我们
See the way those girls drove off? They was laughing at us.
都是你吓走她们
Those girls drove off because of you.
我只想请她们喝杯酒而已
All I did was invite them to have a drink.
你想她们脱光光 然后献祭一头小羊羔
You invited them to get naked and sacrifice a small goat.
哪个字是「羊」
Which word was goat?
你欠我一张《沙滩小子》精选集
You owe me a copy of the Beach Boys' greatest hits.
别给脸色我看
Don't be getting no attitude with me.
我来了三天 都是陪你查案
I been here three days. We done nothing but work your cases.
你说会带我去玩
Only reason I'm here in Hong Kong is you said…
我才来香港
you was gonna show me a good time.
我来度假 想要木须肉
I'm on vacation, man, and I want some mu sh…
木须肉 你肚子饿吗？
Mu shu? You hungry?
李 不是吃木须肉
No, Lee, not mu shu.
是酒池肉林的肉 我想找女人乐一乐
Some mu shu. I wanna see some women, man.
别装傻了 快带我去找美女
Stop playing dumb and show me to the shu.
美国领事馆爆炸了
有两个美国翻译官死了
有没有什么线索
我们认为是谭瑞奇做的
今晚 他全部帮派兄弟
会在那个夜总会
如果你不愿接这个案件
我会明白的
我马上去看看
什么事？
What was that?
我来度假 你又接了另一桩案子
Did you just take another damn case on my vacation, man?
当然没有 我上司请我们去夜总会
Of course not. My superintendent invited us to a club.
- 今晚有个大派对 - 别耍我啊
- Big party tonight. - Don't be messing with me, Lee.
否则我一巴掌把你打回明朝
I will slap you so hard, you'll end up in the Ming dynasty.
真的啊 我还能一巴掌把你扇回曼谷
I mean it, man. I'll bitchslap you back to Bangkok.
- 大派对 - 很大的
- Big party? - Big one.
好吧 那我们去派对吧
Okay, well, let's go party then.
这里不错 喂 美女
Hey, this is nice. Hey, cutie.
她们不喜欢游客 扮作本地人吧
They don't like tourists in here, so try to blend in.
扮本地人 我比所有人高两个头
What, blend in? I'm 2 feet taller than everybody in here.
在这里等我
Wait here.
- 你去哪 - 厕所
- Where you going? - Bathroom.
快点回来 我们要玩个痛快
Well, hurry back, man, because we're gonna party.
超爽的
Party!
∮ 爱 ∮
∮ Love ∮
你好吗
How you doing?
你常来吗？这地方不错
Come here a lot? It's a nice place.
∮ 带我们度过时光 ∮
∮ Take us through the hours ∮
∮ 我不会逼你的，宝贝 ∮
∮ I won't make you, baby ∮
台上搞什么鬼
What in the world is going on up in here?
只有我在听这东西吗
Am I the only one listening to this?
他毁了这首经典金曲
The man destroying a classic!
∮ 给原力不要停下 ∮
∮ To the force don't stop ∮
∮ 不吃饱就不要停下来 ∮
∮ Don't stop till you get enough ∮
∮ 保持原力不要停止 ∮
∮ Keep on to the force don't stop ∮
∮ 不吃饱就不要停下来 ∮
∮ Don't stop till you get enough ∮
∮ 直到原力不停 ∮
∮ Till the force don't stop ∮
∮ 不吃饱就不要停下来 ∮
∮ Don't stop till you get enough ∮
我实在受不了了
Keep on I can't take no more of this.
∮ 靠近一点 ∮
∮ Get closer ∮
∮ 哦，靠近一点 ∮
∮ Oh, get closer ∮
∮ 我现在在燃烧 ∮
∮ I'm burnin' now ∮
∮ 只是爱我 ∮
∮ Just love me ∮
∮ 直到你不知道 ∮
∮ Till you don't know how ∮
∮ 保持原力，不要停下 ∮
∮ Keep on to the force, don't stop ∮
∮ 不吃饱就不要停下来 ∮
∮ Don't stop till you get enough ∮
∮ 继续直到原力开始 ∮
∮ Keep on till the force starts up ∮
∮ 啊，等你够了再停 ∮
∮ Ah, don't stop till you get enough ∮
∮ 继续直到原力开始 ∮
∮ Keep on till the force starts up ∮
来吧 女孩来吧
Oh, come on, girls!
∮ 来吧，直到原力开始 ∮
∮ Come on, till the force starts up ∮
∮ 啊，在你之前别停下 ∮
∮ Ah, don't stop till you ∮
来吧
Come on! Come on!
来吧 女孩
Come here, girls.
∮ 直到你停下来 ∮
∮ Don't stop till you ∮
来吧 女孩
Come on, girl!
∮ 我真不敢相信 ∮
∮ I can't believe it ∮
快来啊
Come on, come on, come on.
别停 来吧
Don't stop, come on.
你已经被我电到
You know you feel the force!
∮ 哦，喔，等你够了再停 ∮
∮ Oh, whoa Don't stop till you get enough ∮
我感到电力十足
I feel the force!
- 卡特 - 来吧
- Carter! - Come on!
- 来吧 - 卡特
- Come on! - Carter!
- 来吧 李 - 卡特
- Come on, Lee! - Carter!
- 来吧 来吧 - 卡特
- Come on! Come on! - Carter!
来吧
Come on!
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
这些人超爱我的 快跟我上台
Lee, these people love me, man. Come on out here.
下来
Get off the stage.
你疯了吗 我可是个明星
Are you crazy, man? I'm a star!
这些人超级崇拜我的 来看看
I'm a god to these people. Come check this out.
这是黑帮酒吧 我们来查案的
This is a gangster bar. We are here undercover.
我就知道你说谎 我一早就知道
I knew you was lying. I knew you was lying, man.
对不起 卡特
I'm sorry, Carter.
你这个骗子 我们来找谭瑞奇
You a liar! We are here to find Ricky Tan.
我们要低调行事
We must tread softly.
低调行事 你说什么呢
Tread softly? What in the world you talking about?
谁教你这样查酒吧的 还低调行事呢
Who taught you how to roust a bar? Tread softly.
他们是三合会 中国最大的帮派
These men are Triads, the most deadly gang in China.
以为那会吓倒我吗
You think that scare me?
帮派是我们洛杉矶发明的
I'm from Los Angeles. We invented gangs.
- 警章给我 我给你看看 - 不 你在这儿是平民
- Give me that badge. I'll show youNo. - You are civilian!
在香港我是周星驰 你是「石斑鱼」
In Hong Kong, I'm Michael Jackson! You are Toto!
你是说「跟班的」吧 石斑鱼是我们昨晚的晚餐
You mean Tito! Toto is what we ate last night for dinner.
- 把警章给我 拿来 - 不
- Now give me that badge. Give it. - No!
好 大家听着
Okay, listen up!
现在
Right now!
- 我说了什么 - 你叫大家…
- What did I just say? - You just asked everybody…
拿起武士刀去切你的屁股
to pick up their samurai swords and shave your butt.
- 我那样说的 - 是的
- I said that? - Yes.
上来帮我翻译
Come out here and translate this for me.
好 大家听着
All right, listen up!
所有三合会和丑女人来这一边
All the Triads and the ugly women on this side…
所有美女来另一边 立刻照做
and all the fine women on this side right now!
翻译
Translate it.
他说所有男士站这里
女士站那里
好 你们假装听不到我说话
Y'all gonna act like y'all don't hear what I'm saying.
谁认识谭瑞奇 认识的举手
All right, who in here know Ricky Tan? Raise your hand.
翻译
Translate.
各位对不起 我朋友今天喝多了 现在有点傻傻的
我明白发生什么事了
I see what's going on here.
好
Okay.
我没时间玩游戏了
I ain't got time to be playing no games now.
- 我要… - 胡莉
- I'm taking. - Hu Li!
等一下 嘿 李
Wait. Hey, Lee!
让开 洛杉矶警察
Out of the Way! L.A.P.D.!
李 等等
Lee! Hold up!
还是算了吧
Aw, hell no. Uhuh.
我走楼梯
Lee, I'm taking the stairs!
走开点 科比
老伯对不起 继续吃饭
卡特
Carter!
我在这里
Over here!
- 李 - 救我
- Lee! - Help me!
你怎样下去的
How you get down there?
快点
Hurry UP!
抓紧
Hold on!
别放手
Don't let go, man.
来 小心你后面
Here. Watch out! Behind you!
- 你后面 - 什么
- Huh? Behind you! - What?
那到底是谁
Who the hell was that?
老天爷啊 我不想死
Lord Jesus, I don't wanna die!
李 救救我
Lee, help me, man!
别担心 中国的竹子是很结实的
Don't worry. Chinese bamboo is very strong.
- 你确定吗？- 我确定
- You sure, man? - I'm sure.
李
Lee!
放手
Let go! Let go!
我真不敢相信我飞了一万英里 就为了来搅这滩浑水
I can't believe I flew 10, 000 miles for this shit!
你竟然骗我
I can't believe you lied to me, man.
- 对不起 - 对不起？
- I'm sorry. - You're sorry?
我被粗筷子插屁股
I got somebody's old chopsticks stuck up my ass…
而你只说声对不起
all you gotta say to me is you sorry?
- 发生了爆炸事件 - 关我屁事
- There was an explosion. - I don't give a damn!
是美国领事馆 死了两个美国人
At the American embassy. Two Americans were killed.
你认为是谭瑞奇干的
So you think this guy Ricky Tan blew up the embassy?
我不知道
I don't know.
那你为什么要找他
Why the hell are you looking for him then?
- 我们找到他就知道了 - 是「你」自己去找他
- We're gonna find out. - No, you gonna find out, man.
有二十亿中国人呢 随便找个人做你搭档吧
There's two billion Chinese people here. Let one of them be your partner.
- 我们在什么鬼地方 - 桑拿浴室
- Where the hell we at now? - Massage parlor.
天上人间
Heaven on Earth.
这还差不多
Now, this is more like it.
我现在就要去享受按摩
I'm about to go in here and get a massage…
和热茶浴
and a hot tea bath right now.
依我指示行事 扮作游客
Just follow my lead. Act like a tourist.
我本来就是游客 白痴
I am a tourist, fool.
慢一点 你有病啊
Hey! Slow down, Chen! Hell is wrong with you?
- 好 - 我的美国朋友在度假
- Yeah. - My American friend is on vacation.
我想带他找找乐子
I wanna show him a good time.
噢 你是美国人
Oh, you American.
- 是啊 - 你带了美金吗？
- Yeah. - You bring American money?
- 李 我请 - 不要
- I got it, Lee. - No.
- 我来就好 - 你确定吗？
- I got it. - You sure?
确定
I'm sure.
- 谢谢 - 不用客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
两位先生 请来这边
Right this way, gentlemen.
你们准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗？我准备好了
You ready? I'm ready.
我的天
Oh, my goodness!
这地方简直好得冒泡 我爱香港
This place is off the hook! I love Hong Kong.
你试过被中国女郎按摩吗？
You get massage from Chinese girl before?
没有 我听说会令人欲仙欲死
No, but I heard it was the bomb.
跟我来
Come with me.
你给自己和你朋友挑个女孩吧
You pick any girl for you and your friend.
- 任何一个 - 任何一个
- Any girl? - Any girl.
好
Okay.
我都不知道要挑谁了
I don't know where to start.
- 我挑那边那个吧 - 对 她很不错
- I'll take that one. She got to come. - Oh, yes, she's very nice.
她确实不错 但我扭伤了背和脖子
She is nice, but I hurt my back and my neck…
要多点按摩
I need a little bit more massage.
我也要粉红色那个
So I'm gonna take her in the pink too.
- 好的 - 还有她 喂 美女
- Oh, yes. - Let me get her. Hey, baby.
我还要她 我可以挑她吗？
And then let me have her. Can I get her too?
那边那位 她脚底按摩拿手吗？
And her right there. She good with feet?
- 拿手 - 你干什么
- Oh, yes. - What are you doing?
她说可以随便挑
She said I could have any girl I want in here. Wait.
那就快点啊
Well, hurry up!
你不能在秀色可餐的肉林面前 催黑人兄弟
Man, you don'tjump in front of a black man in a buffet line.
冷静一点
Calm down!
我得 你的朋友胃口很大啊
I have toYour friend has big appetite.
请跟她上楼去安静的房间
Please, follow her upstairs into the quiet room.
那间房不会再静了
It ain't gonna be no quiet room no more.
还有
And oh.
你们不知道这有多舒服
Y'all don't know how good this feels.
我昨晚跟三合会大打出手
I got in a big fight last night with the Triads.
听说过三合会吗？我一个人击退了20人
Ever heard of the Triads? I beat down like 20 of them.
可惜你们看不到我多厉害
Y'all should've seen me, it was on. Oh.
- 李 李 - 什么事
- Lee.Lee. - Yeah?
这才像样
This is what I'm talking about, man.
现在我才感觉在度假
Now I'm on vacation.
我知道你不会令我失望的
I knew you'd come through. I just knew it.
美国
America?
想跟我回美国
Wanna come to America with me?
去过美国没有
Ever been to America?
李 你的女孩怎么样
Lee, how's your girl?
- 李 怎么了 - 那是谭瑞奇
- Lee, what's wrong? - That's Ricky Tan.
谭瑞奇 那个穿浴袍的小侏儒
That's Ricky Tan? That's a midget in a bathrobe!
我去叫后援
I will call for backup.
他才四英尺高 我们去抓住他
Lee, the man is 4 feet tall. Let's go bust him right now.
- 不 - 不
- No. - No?
他是危险人物
He's a very dangerous man.
我也是危险人物
I'm a very dangerous man.
我们过去抓住他
Now, look, let's go over there and bust him, man.
你别打扰我按摩
You're not about to mess up my massage.
- 留在这里 - 你不需要后援
- Stay here. - You don't need backup.
我就是你的后…
I got your back.
失陪一分钟 一分钟就好
Excuse me for a minute. Just for a minute.
我会回来的
I'll be back. Don't.
我很快回来
I'll be back.
瑞奇 谭瑞奇
Ricky? Ricky Tan?
起来吧 老兄 我到处找你
Get up, dog. I've been looking for you everywhere.
我现在很忙
I'm busy at the moment.
你听到我讲话吗？我也很忙 站起来
Did you hear what I said? I'm busy too. Now get on your feet.
起来 站起来
Get up! Get on your feet!
我认识你 你是李的美国朋友 对吗？
I know you. You are Lee's American friend, right?
不 我是李的新保镖 别因这浴袍的颜色而小看我
No. I'm Lee's new muscle. And don't let this robe fool you.
他们只剩下这个颜色 我叫你站起来
This is the only color they had left. Now I said, get up.
我不会再说一次
I ain't gonna say it again.
你们美国人真滑稽
You American are so funny.
你们亚洲人都耳背啊
And you Asians don't hear that well.
小瑞奇
Little Ricky.
把你的混帐屁股
Get your little punk ass up…
离开那张椅子
out of that chair right now!
你破坏我的假期 我叫你站起来 听到吗？
You're messing up my vacation. Now, I told you to get up, didn't I?
- 现在我不得不发飙了 - 别
- Now I gotta go off on you. - No.
让我来收拾他 拜托
Let me bust his ass.
让我来教训他
Let me take care of this.
好久没见你了 你好吗
我有些事情想问你
什么事
请你跟我回警察局
是关于两个美国人被杀的事
这么严重
有什么事情你可以在这里跟我说
听着 小矮子 跟我走
Look, little man. You coming with.
我的天
Oh, my Lord.
我想赔你笔记本电脑 我必须得陪
I would like to pay you for that laptop. I think I should do that.
- 不用了 - 赔最新的
- No problem. - I can get you a new one.
我在网上见到有款可以放DVD的
Seen it on the internet with DVD player.
你那台是旧款 现在请恕失陪了
That's an old model. Now, I must excuse myself.
督察
Inspector.
玩开心点
Have a good day.
我只是
I was…
你干嘛不告诉我他那么人强马壮
Lee, why didn't you tell me this man rolls like this?
- 我告诉过你 - 不 你没有
- I told you! - You didn't!
- 我有 - 你说过什么
- I did. - What you said?
- 我做过这个表情 - 那表示什么
- I did this. - What do "this" mean, man?
- 用英文说 - 表示我去这边
- Speak English to me! - That means I go this way…
- 你去那边 - 我去那边 你去这边
- you, this way. - I go that way, you, this way?
- 是 - 好的
- Yes. - Okay.
- 不好意思 你们样子都差不多 - 卡特
- Unh! Sorry, man. All y'all look alike! - Carter!
小心
Watch out!
卡特
Carter!
李
Lee!
怪不得你生气
Oh! No wonder you mad.
别担心 没事的
Don't worry. It's okay.
你还是出去一下比较好
You better get the hell out of here.
李
Lee!
- 翻转我 - 什么
- Flip me! - What?
翻转我
Flip me!
该死
Damn!
李
Lee!
不…不
No, no, no! No!
- 李 - 小心
- Lee! - Watch out!
李
Lee!
不 公安局命令你
No, no. Look, you've been ordered by the Ministry of Public Security…
协助联邦调查局和特勤局查案
to assist the FBI and Secret Service in our investigation…
提供我们一切所需
to provide us with whatever we need.
若你有情报 一定要告诉我们
You have information, it belongs to us.
这里是香港
This is still Hong Kong.
两个美国人在美国政府大楼被杀
Two Americans have been killed on United States government property.
给我两份影本
Give me two copies of that.
这是我们的案件
This is our investigation.
李总督察会指挥你的人员
Chief Inspector Lee will supervise your people.
不 他要听我指挥 你明白吗？
No, he will report to me. Do we understand each other?
这位是何方神圣
What the hell is that?
那是李总督察
That is, uh, Chief Inspector Lee.
我一生从没感到
Ain't never been humiliated and embarrassed like that…
这么尴尬及耻辱
in my whole entire life.
脱光光在香港到处跑 多谢你了
Got me running around Hong Kong buttnaked, thanks to you.
- 多谢我？- 对 多多感谢你
- Thanks to me? - Yeah, thanks to you.
你要后援 我说给你后援
You needed backup, so I gave you backup.
我快要痛扁谭瑞奇 和他的小弟们了
I was about to kick Ricky Tan's ass, and his bodyguards'…
- 你却来坏事 - 别说了
- till you messed it up. - Stop.
- 我受够你的废话了 - 是我受够你了
- I'm sick of your bullshit. - I'm sick of you!
不是我要去黑帮酒吧
I'm not the one running up in karaoke bars full of gangsters.
不是我要去桑拿浴室找犯罪头子
I'm not the one running up in massage parlors looking for crime lords.
- 这是我的职责所在 - 职责
- It's my job. - It's your job.
真可怜 你何时才能去找找乐子
You pitiful, man. When are you gonna have some fun?
你何时才能休个假 去约约会
When are you gonna take a day off? Go on a date or something?
- 我有很多约会 - 什么时候
- I have plenty of dates. - When?
你上次约会是何时你倒是说啊
When's the last time you had a date, huh?
你上次玩「滚床单」是何时
When's the last time you played Hide the Rainbow Roll, huh?
说来听听 是鼠年那年吗？
Let's hear it, Lee. The year of the rat?
你永远不会了解我
You will never understand me.
对 我连你刚才说什么也不了解
You right. I didn't even understand what you just said to me right then.
我的护照留在桑拿浴室
They got my passport back at that massage parlor.
午安
Good afternoon, sir.
- 李 - 是的 长官
- Lee. - Yes, sir.
这位是美国特勤局的史特林
This is Special Agent Sterling from the United States Secret Service.
特勤局 为什么
Secret Service? Why?
请坐
Have a seat, please.
我准备告诉你的事必须保密
What I'm about to tell you cannot leave this room.
昨天被杀的并非美国翻译员
The men who were killed yesterday were not American translators.
他们是美国海关的卧底探员
They were undercover United States customs agents…
任务是粉碎一个三合会走私集团
trying to break a Triad smuggling ring.
- 走私什么 - 我们不知道
- Smuggling what? - We don't know.
无论走私什么 导致他们被杀有关
But whatever it is, it got the agents killed.
我们可以怎么协助
How can we help you?
只要你别妨碍我们办事
You can stay the hell out of our way.
谢谢
Thank you.
我可以给你谭瑞奇的情报
I can get you Ricky Tan.
不必 我们对他了如指掌
No. We know all about Tan.
所以我们放他在外边作饵
That's why we're leaving him out there as bait.
幕后组织比谭瑞奇的福苍龙帮大得多
This is a lot bigger than Ricky Tan and the Fu Cang Long Triads.
喂 美女
Hey, cutie.
多谢 李
Thank you, Lee.
卡特 卡特
Carter! Carter!
天上人间桑拿浴室
Uh, Heaven on Earth massage parlor?
天上人间
Heaven on Earth?
喂 便宜唐装
Hello. Cheap suits.
Hello. Cheap suits. Cheap suits.
便宜唐装
Cheap suits. Cheap suits.
- 有多便宜 - 便宜唐装
- How cheap? - Cheap suits.
便宜到死
Cheap as hell?
不好意思
Excuse me.
请问
Can you direct me…
天上人间桑拿浴室在哪
to Heaven on Earth massage parlor, please?
- 哈罗 你好吗 - 很好
- Hello. How are you? - Okay.
不 等一下
No, no. Wait a minute.
不不 我不要鸡
No. I don't want no chicken.
不
No, no, no. Aah!
不 我不要鸡 我要只鸡来干嘛
No! I don't want no chicken. What am I gonna do with a chicken?
我不喜欢活鸡 好吗
I don't like my chickens live, okay?
我喜欢油炸的死鸡 听过大力水手炸鸡吗？
I like them dead and deepfried. You ever heard of Popeye's?
不 不 不
No, no! No!
别杀那只鸡
Heh. Don't kill chicken.
我警告你
Aah! I'm warning you.
我是警察 放下刀 放开那只鸡
I'm a police officer. Put the blade down and let the bird go right now!
李 你没事吧
You okay, Lee?
他只是想吃木须肉罢了
All he wanted was some mu shu.
妈的
Damn.
喂 计程车
Hey, taxi! Taxi!
嘿
Hey! Hey!
跟着那车
Follow that car.
跟着那辆礼车 我要追他 明白吗？
Hey, follow that limo. This is a chase, okay?
他去哪里 你都要跟着
Wherever he goes, you go.
你没在动啊 这跟「追」是相反的啊
You're not moving! This is the opposite of chasing!
什么 你再不开我就揍你
What? I will slap you if you don't move this car.
我要揍你啦
I'm gonna slap you. I'm gonna slap you.
好 听着
Okay. All right. Okay, look.
给你 现在听得懂吗
Here. You understand that?
我现在懂你说什么了
Now you're speaking my language.
开车呀 快点 走
Get the hell on then. Come on, Let's go!
香港水警刚有电话来说谭瑞奇
会在船上开派对 我想自己去看看
你有没有通知史特林
没有通知他
我要香港警方自己来处理
在这里等我 我立刻回来
Wait right here. I'll be right back.
- 明白吗？- 明白
- You understand? - Yes, I understand.
- 别吃我的鸡 好吗 - 好的
- And don't eat my chicken, okay? - Okay, okay.
- 好的 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay.
天啊
Jesus.
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
你好吗 宝贝
How you doing, baby?
我是卡特 詹姆斯卡特 来自鲍德温山
Carter. James Carter. Baldwin hills.
伊莎贝拉莫莉娜 圣胡安来的
Isabella Molina. From San Juan.
圣胡安
San Juan? Mmhm.
我知道 我搭我的私人飞机 去过好几次
I know San Juan. I've traveled there many times on my private plane.
你一定认识我朋友
You must know my good friend…
佩德罗莫拉莱斯麻冈萨雷斯 莫兰多莫拉索蒙多斯托斯
Pedro Morales Magonzales Marato Molaso Mondustos.
- 我不认识 - 你确定吗？
- I don't think so, no. - You sure?
对不起 我以为你很熟上流社会
Mmhm. Well, I'm sorry. I thought you rode in the best of circles.
不过 当自己家好了
But listen, make yourself feel at home.
不管你需要什么 香槟 鱼子酱
You need anything, champagne, caviar…
我的游艇就是你的
my yacht is your yacht.
这艘游艇是你的吗
This is your yacht?
对 我是船主
That's right. I'm the owner.
船长
The captain.
听着
Yes. Listen.
我不想跟你玩游戏 我现在就想要你
I'm not gonna play games with you. I want you, right now.
我可以想像我们五分钟后
I see me and you downstairs in one of those bathrooms…
在楼下浴室打得火热
in about five minutes.
我很心动 这艘船这么美
Well, I'm very tempted. It's such a beautiful yacht.
它叫什么名字
What's it called?
- 它叫什么名字 - 你的游艇
- What's it called? - Mmhm. Your yacht.
SS米诺强森
The S.S. Minnow Johnson.
- SS米诺强森吗？- 对
- The S.S. Minnow Johnson? - Yeah.
奇怪 船尾明明写着赤龙
Funny. The name on the back was the Red Dragon.
赤龙 你确定吗？
The Red Dragon? Are you sure?
我确定
Oh, I'm sure.
因为这是我朋友的游艇
Because this is my friend's yacht.
- 你朋友的游艇 - 这是他的派对
- Your friend's yacht? - And this is his party.
我确定是上错船了
I must've got on the wrong yacht.
这些船都差不多
All these yachts look just alike these days.
我的锁匙开不了门时 就知道不对劲
I knew something was wrong when my key didn't work.
- 你这位朋友是谁 - 上错船的人
- Who's your friend? - Somebody who got on the wrong yacht.
等等 我认识你 史蒂芬瑞恩 对吗
Hey, wait a second. I know you. Steven Reign, right?
你拥有半个洛杉矶 来香港干吗？
You own half of Los Angeles. What you doing out here in Hong Kong?
度周末 看风景
I'm here for the weekend, taking in the sights.
你一定也有私人飞机了 很过瘾吧
You must have your own plane too. It's fun, ain't it?
- 我们走走好吗 - 好
- Shall we? - Yes.
玩开心点 卡特先生
Well, enjoy the party, Mr. Carter.
我正有此意 伊莎贝拉小姐
I plan to, Miss Isabella.
待会见 史蒂芬 保重
See you later, Stevie. Be cool.
谭瑞奇在哪
Ricky Tan. Where is he?
我不知道
I don't know!
他今天杀了一个探员 他在哪
He killed a detective today. Where is he?
谁被杀了
Who got killed, man?
- 卡特 - 李 谁死了
- Carter! - Who died, Lee?
- 你 - 倪探员
- You! - Detective Yu?
不是倪 是你
Not Yu, you!
- 谁 - 你
- Who? - You!
谁
Who?
你明不明白我嘴巴说出来的话
Do you understand the words that are coming out of my mouth?
没人会明白你嘴巴说出来的话
Don't nobody understand the words that are coming out of your mouth, man.
谭瑞奇在等你
Ricky Tan is waiting for you.
李 这里到底发生什么事
What the hell is going on here, Lee?
记得我告诉过你我爸爸是警察吗
Remember I told you my father was a policeman?
- 对 - 谭瑞奇是他的搭档
- Yeah. - Ricky Tan was his partner.
什么
What?
胡莉 别跟我胡说八道
你忘记你从哪来的
怎么了 你长大了现在
有翅膀 你可以飞了
给我滚 他妈的
李 我在等你 叫你搭档在里面等吧
Lee, I've been expecting you. Please ask your partner to wait inside.
- 不 我哪儿也不去 - 没事的
- Hell, no. I ain't going nowhere. - It's okay.
- 李 我不会留下你一个 - 我不会有事
- I'm not leaving you alone, Lee. - I'll be fine.
- 你确定吗 - 确定
- You sure? - Yes.
我在楼上等你
I'll be right upstairs.
我听到谣言
I know what everybody's saying.
领事馆不是我炸的
I did not blow up the American embassy.
我没那么笨
I'm not that stupid.
但我相信是我手下做的
But I believe some of my people did.
我的死对头想嫁祸我
My enemies are trying to frame me.
现在三合会正在起内哄
There is a war going on right now within the Triads.
恐怕这次我会输
I'm afraid I'm gonna lose this time.
你父亲若还活着 我会求教于他
If your father were still alive, I would turn to him for advice.
请你别提他
Please don't.
李 我需要你帮忙 我信不过别人
Lee, I really need your help. I cannot trust anybody else.
告诉我他们为何要杀海关人员
Tell me why they killed the customs agents.
你要什么情报我都可以给你
I'll give you all the information you need.
但你要立刻把我弄离香港
But you've gotta get me out of Hong Kong right away.
你在做什么
Hey, lady, what are you doing?
下来 我是洛杉矶警察
Get down. I'm L.A.P.D.
你刚刚踢我吗
You just kick me?
你一定是疯了
You must be out of your mind!
你想挑战我
You want some of me?
想试试洛杉矶警察的厉害吗
I'm gonna give you an L.A.P.D. asskicking!
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
我滑倒了
I slipped and I fell.
- 嘿 - 怎么了
- Hey. - What?
我有流血吗？
Am I bleeding?
督察 今晚很热闹啊
Quite a night, inspector.
谭瑞奇是我们唯一的饵 现在他死了
Ricky Tan was our only bait. Now he's gone.
你的仇报了
So you got your revenge.
代价是毁了美国政府的调查
At the expense of a United States government investigation.
报仇 你说什么
Revenge? What are you talking about, revenge?
我搞不清楚是三合会 收买你去杀谭瑞奇
Now, I don't know if the Triads paid you to get rid of Tan…
或是你纯为了报复而杀人
or if it was a pure vendetta killing…
又或者你根本与走私有关
or if you're involved in the smuggling yourself.
但你别再碰此案
But you're off this case.
我不想再见到你 清楚了吗
I don't ever wanna see you again. Is that clear?
- 嘿 发生了什么事 - 卡特 你已经惹了够多麻烦了
- Hey, what's going on here? - Carter, you're in enough trouble.
就闭嘴吧
Just shut up.
少管闲事
Stay out of it.
你立刻回洛杉矶
You're going back to L.A. right now.
好啊 反正来这里之后 玩得也不开心
Hey, that's fine with me, man. I ain't had fun since I been out here.
好了
Okay.
李 对不起
Sorry, Lee.
- 护送卡特探员去机场 - 不
- Escort Detective Carter to the airport. - No.
我送他
I'll take him.
你们给我放手
Get your hands off!
你不明白
Carter, you don't understand.
我完全明白
Oh, I understand all right.
我被人推下楼 被殴打
I got knocked off a building, I got beat on…
被扒光 而你仍然不肯对我说真话
I got stripped buttnaked, and you held out on me, man.
我走了
I'm out of here.
卡特 谭瑞奇出卖我爸爸
Carter, Ricky Tan set up my father.
什么
What?
五年前我爸在调查一宗国际走私案
Five years ago, my father was working a big international smuggling case.
他发现他的搭档谭瑞奇 原来替三合会卖命
He found out his partner, Tan, was working for the Triads.
但在他找到证据之前就被杀了
But before he could prove it, he was killed.
证据全消失
All the evidence disappeared.
谭辞职 留下悬案
Tan resigned, and the case was never solved.
我明白了 全因你爸爸最后那件案子
So I get it now. This is all about your daddy's last case.
那么你跟我上飞机吗？
So you getting on the plane with me or not?
什么
What?
你知道我爸爸也是殉职的
You know my daddy died on the job too.
如果可以找到凶手 我也会不顾一切
If I had a chance to square his death, I'd do whatever it took.
我会不择手段
I'd do anything.
那你到底来不来
So you coming or what?
为什么要去洛杉矶
Why L.A.?
让我向你简介
Lee, let me introduce you…
卡特的办案理论
to Carter's theory of criminal investigation:
跟踪有钱白人
Follow the rich white man.
- 跟踪有钱白人？- 对 好好学
- Follow the rich white man? - Exactly. Now you're learning.
每桩大案幕后
Every big crime has a rich white man behind it…
都有个有钱白人
waiting for his cut.
就这桩案子来说 我们知道有钱的白人是谁
Now, in our case, we know who the rich white man is.
- 史蒂芬瑞恩 - 谁
- Steven Reign. - Who?
饭店大亨 他在谭瑞奇的船上
Steven Reign, the hotel billionaire. I saw him on Ricky Tan's boat.
枪战发生时 他太冷静了
When the shooting started, he was way too cool.
有人开枪的话 白人不会那么冷静
When people start shooting, white people ain't that cool.
他们会乱窜 躲在桌子底下
They either running around, hiding behind tables…
或像这样尖叫
or screaming like, "Aah"!
你经常那样叫的
Shh. You sound like that all the time.
如果是我们黑人的话
Tell you something about black people.
遇到暴力事件时很冷静
When stuff goes down, we keep our cool.
但不及亚洲人 我们永不恐慌
Maybe, but not like Asians. We never panic.
是吗 哥吉拉来时你们都吓趴下了
Yeah, right. When Godzilla's coming, y'all be tripping.
我看过那部电影
I seen the movie.
- 你会喊 「救命」 - 卡特
- You be, "Gaioa, gaica"! - Carter.
- 到处尖叫 - 就
- Yelling everywhere. - Just.
卡特先生 不好意思
Mr. Carter, excuse me.
谢谢
Thank you so much.
- 这是犹太餐吗？- 是 这是我们提供的犹太餐
- It's the kosher meal? Shalom. - Yes, sir, our kosher meal.
他就在那里 史蒂芬瑞恩先生
There he is. Mr. Steven Reign.
在他的顶楼豪宅内尽享奢华
Living large in one of his penthouse suites.
猜我见到谁是她
Oh, guess who this is. Yep, that's her.
在谭瑞奇游艇上的那个女人
That's the woman that was on Ricky Tan's boat, right there.
找到他们了
We got them.
我就说行得通嘛
Told you it'd work out. Know what I'm talking about.
现在只要等
All we gotta do now is wait.
他们仍在谈话
They still talking? Mmhm.
他要走了
He's leaving.
- 他会回来的 - 你怎么知道的
- He'll be back. - How do you know?
见到那女人多美吗
I know. You see how fine that woman is?
他一定会回来的
He'll definitely be back.
她在干什么
What's she doing?
What's she doing, man?
她只是站着 没做什么
She's just standing around, not doing much.
别睡着
Well, just don't fall asleep.
迟早会有事发生的
Sooner or later, something's gonna happen.
好 我尽量不睡 真是闷死人
Okay, I just try to stay awake. It's just so boring.
慢一点 宝贝
Ah. Slow down, baby.
什么
What?
没什么 我没说话
Huh? Nothing. I said nothing.
- 你说话了 - 没说
- You said something. - I said nothing.
- 我听见你嘀咕什么了 - 没有的事
- I heard you say something. - No, no, no. Nothing.
李 怎么回事 你在干嘛
Lee, what's going on, man? What you talking about?
- 她在脱衣服 - 什么
- She's getting undressed. - What?
- 她正在脱衣服 - 给我那东西
- She's getting undressed. - Give me that.
不
No!
这样很不道德
It's not right!
- 老天爷 放过我 - 什么
- Lord, have mercy! - What?
- 她脱下裙子 - 噢 我不要再听了
- She took her skirt off. - Oh, I cannot hear this.
黑色内裤 黑色胸罩
Black panties, black bra.
维多莉亚的秘密春季目录27页
Victoria's Secret, spring catalog, page 27.
有品味
Girl got class.
让我近一点看
Let me look a little closer.
看那小刺青 真可爱
Oh, look at that. Got a little tattoo. That's cute.
看来像 史努比
Looks like Snoopy.
- 史努比 - 是的
- Snoopy? - Yeah.
- 我爱史努比 - 等等 我也爱史努比
- I love Snoopy. - Wait. I love Snoopy too.
让我看
Let me look at this thing.
等等
Hold up. Wait a minute.
她走向门口了
She's going to the door. Wait. She's going to the door.
她开门了
She's opening the door.
好像有人送来一个包裹
Look like somebody dropping off a package.
等一等
Wait a minute.
好像是和送包裹到你办公室的 是同一个女子
Look like the same girl who dropped off the package at your office.
- 是炸弹 - 炸弹
- It's a bomb! - Bomb!
小心 小心
Watch out! Watch out!
我想是这道门 小姐 有炸弹
It's this one right here, I think. Hey, you got a bomb in there!
开门
Open the door!
踢门吧
Kick the door.
- 怎么回事 - 不
- What the he? - No, no, no!
- 该死 你好美 - 卡特
- Damn, you fine. - Carter!
- 跟我来 李 来 - 去哪儿
- Come on, Lee! Come on! - Where? Where?
- 别丢掉 这边来 - 我们要去哪
- Don't drop it! Come on, this way! - Where should we go?
屋顶
Roof! Roof!
别绊倒小心
Don't trip! Be careful!
- 李 扔掉 - 扔去哪
- Throw it, Lee! - Where?
- 扔出去 - 扔哪儿啊
- Throw it! - Where?
把炸弹从大厦边缘扔出去扔啊
Throw the bomb over the edge! Throw it.
把炸弹从大厦边扔出去
Throw it! Throw it over the edge!
- 不 下面很多人 - 扔呀
- There's people down there! - Throw it!
- 卡特 - 李
- Carter! Carter! - Lee!
- 李 - 卡特
- Lee! - Carter!
- 扔啊 - 不
- Throw it! - No!
我们快要死了
We about to die!
好吧 站起来
Okay, get on your feet.
- 玩够了吧 - 放下它
- Enough! - Put that down!
- 那是炸弹 - 放下它
- It's a bomb! hey! - Put that down!
两位 没有炸弹 什么也没有
Guys, no bomb. Nothing.
再搅局我就抓你们去坐牢 告你们妨碍执法
Now stay away before I throw you both in jail for obstruction.
抓我们去坐牢
Throw us in jail?
你疯了 我才正要抓你呢
You must be out of your mind. I'm about to bust you right now.
我是美国特勤局的卧底探员
I'm an undercover agent for the United States Secret Service.
我们怎知道真假 拿徽章来看看
How do we know that? Show me a badge.
看吧
Here you go.
让我再看一次 我没看清楚
Let me see that again. I didn't get a good look at that.
我们可以帮你 我是香港来的探员
We can help you. I'm a detective from Hong Kong.
我知道你是谁 李督察
I know who you are, Inspector Lee. I know.
我们要避人耳目
We need to go out of sight.
下去我房间吧
So come down to my suite.
- 你干嘛说那是炸弹 - 是你说的
- Now why did you say it was a bomb? - No, you said that.
- 不 是你 - 你在酒店房里说的
- No, you said it. - You said that in the hotel room.
我说她是肉弹
I said she was the bomb.
她是肉弹
She was the bomb?
我查这案子已经几个月了
Now, look, I've been working this case for months now.
- 若我刚才发了脾气 我道歉 - 你要告诉我们是怎么回事
- So if I seem aggravated, I apologize. - You need to tell us what's going on.
三合会和瑞恩以为我是贪污的关员
The Triads and Reign, they think I'm a crooked customs agent.
那些钱是贿款吗？
Is that a payoff?
不 那是样本
No. That's a sample.
你们有听过超级钞票吗？
You guys ever heard of the Superbill?
那是神话 伪钞的一种吧
Yeah. It's a myth. Some kind of counterfeit.
那并非一般的伪钞
Honey, it's much more than a counterfeit.
十五家世界银行中 有十四家分辨不出差别
Fourteen out of 15 world banks can't even tell the difference.
用美钞专用纸
The paper is Crane linen blend…
及美钞印钞机印的
and the bills are printed on U.S. intaglio presses.
他们怎么进入美国造币厂用印钞机
Tell us how they get into the U.S. mint to use the presses.
1959年 美国跟伊朗王十分友好
In 1959, the United States was very friendly with the shah of Iran.
为什么 因为我们想要他的石油
Why? Because we wanted his oil.
我国政府送了他一份礼物
Our government gave him a gift.
美国的印钞机
A U.S. treasury intaglio printing press.
那是唯一一部离开美国本土的
Now, it's the only one to ever leave the country.
五年前 谭瑞奇从黑市买到那部机器
Five years ago, Ricky bought the press on the black market.
- 五年前 - 嗯
- Five years ago? - Mmhm.
- 正是他离开警方之前 - 今年初
- That's right before he left the force. - Earlier this year, Ricky Tan got ahold…
谭瑞奇得到瑞士制的百元钞票印版
of Swissmade hundred dollar plates…
于是他便开始印超级钞票
and he started printing Superbills.
胡莉为了印版杀他
That's why Hu Li killed him. For the plates.
他们已印制和运走了一亿元
And they've printed and shipped $100 million.
只有一个方法分辨真伪
There's only one way to spot a fake.
他们用印度油墨 烧起来会变红色
They use an optical transfer ink from India that burns red.
而真钞烧起来是黑色的
You see? Now, the real ink, it burns black.
他们打算用一亿元伪钞来干什么
So, what in the hell they gonna do with a hundred million of phony money?
卡特 我相信你问错了
You know, Carter, I believe you're asking the wrong question.
你该问印版在哪
The real question is where are the plates?
因找到印版 就可制止整个行动
If we can find the plates, we can stop the whole operation.
- 对吗 - 对 你说得对
- Right? - Yeah, you're right.
也许有一个办法你们可帮忙
Maybe this is where you can help us, guys.
卡特 这是你的地头 对吗
Yeah. I mean, Carter, this is your city, right?
对 这是我乳头 不 地头
Yeah, this is my titty. I mean, this is my city.
好
Great.
李 你认识胡莉和三合会吧
And Lee, you know Hu Li and the Triads, correct?
- 认识 - 好极了
- Yes. - Great.
帮我个忙 好吗？
So can you do me a favor?
你们可否帮我查出 胡莉把印版藏在哪
Can you find out where Hu Li's keeping the plates?
没问题 谢谢
That ain't no problem.Thank you.
两位 欢迎加入
So welcome aboard, gentlemen.
从这刻起 你们就为
From this moment on, you're officially working…
特勤局工作
for the United States Secret Service.
特勤局探员詹姆斯卡特
Secret Service agent James Carter.
真好听 听起来很顺耳吧
Aw, that sounds good. It's got a nice ring to it, don't it?
不出六个月
I'm telling you, give me six months. Six months.
我便会升去华盛顿保护总统
I'm gonna be in Washington, D.C. protecting the president.
我们都知道 你从不为别人挡子弹
We both know you would never take a bullet for someone else.
对 但他们不知道
Yeah, but they don't know that.
我去问问伊莎贝拉 有没有门路
I'm gonna talk to Isabella, see if she can hook something up.
我见到她望着我的样子
Seeing the way she was staring at a brother.
她连看也没看你一眼
She never even looked at you.
李 你妒忌了吧 因她看中我
Just jealous, Lee, because the girl chose me.
我魁梧英俊 皮肤古铜 你是第三世界的丑男
Because I'm tall, dark and handsome. And you Third World ugly.
我才不丑 女人都很喜欢我
I'm not Third World ugly. Women like me.
她们觉得我很可爱 像史努比
They think I'm cute, like Snoopy.
史努比比你还高六寸
Lee, Snoopy is 6 inches taller than you.
- 史特林 - 李和卡特正式
- Sterling. - Lee and Carter are officially…
不会妨碍特勤局了 没错
out of the Secret Service's way. Correct.
（克伦萧厨房 正宗中式料理）
这是我线人的餐馆 排骨相当不错
This is my informant's place. They got pretty good ribs here too.
我喜欢犹太餐
I like kosher.
喂 等等
Hey. Hey, wait.
我就知道我没想到眼前会是这幅情景
Oh, I know I don't think I see what I see what I'm thinking!
我知道你们都不是在赌钱
I know good and well y'all ain't gambling back here!
这可是中国餐馆啊
This is supposed to be a Chinese restaurant!
你来干嘛 詹姆斯
What you doing in here, James?
你和你的朋友快要坐牢了 大家收拾东西
You about to go to jail. You about to go to jail, and all your little friends.
- 离开这里 - 好了
- Pack up your stuff! Let's go! - All right.
- 我们外面谈吧 - 你想去外面谈
- Let's talk outside. - You wanna talk outside?
- 对 - 走吧 你想谈我奉陪
- Yes. - Let's go then. You wanna talk.
只要你想谈就好
As long as you wanna talk.
你哪里买的这件衣服 不错哦
Where you get that from? I like that.
真不错 你好吗 肯尼
That's good. What's up, Kenny?
- 詹姆斯卡特 - 怎么了
- James Carter. - What's up?
我听说你在香港被打了
I heard you was getting your ass kicked out there in Hong Kong.
- 什么 - 没错
- What? - That's right.
- 你疯了 谁告诉你的 - 我有线人
- You crazy. Who told you that? - I got my sources.
- 你就别担心了 - 他们说谎
- Don't you worry about that. - They telling you lies.
你不给我情报我就抓你去坐牢
I'm about to bust you if you don't give me some information.
你干嘛跑来这样恐吓我
How you gonna come up here and jam me up like this, James? Huh?
你在我老婆孩子面前丢我脸
You embarrass me in front of my wife, my kids out there.
你自己丢脸
Kenny, you embarrassing yourself.
黑人在克伦萧黑人区开中国餐厅
You a black man with a Chinese restaurant on Crenshaw.
你闯进来 又没出示警章
You come up in here, you ain't show me no badge.
连搜查令也没秀一下
You ain't even flashed a warrant.
你知道我要干什么吗 打得你满地找牙
Know what I'm gonna do for you? I'm gonna whup your ass.
然后再打得你满地找牙
And then I'm gonna whup your ass.
肯尼 我们倒想见识见识 来吧
Kenny, we'd love to see that. We would want.
- 来啊 肯尼 - 来啊
- Come on, Kenny! Come on, Kenny! - Come on!
开枪啊 我会开枪 然后说你在厨房跌倒
Do it! I'll shoot, say you fell in the kitchen.
- 来啊 - 你最好冷静点
- Come on! - You better chill out, boy.
- 肯尼 冷静点 - 嘿 怎么
- Kenny, calm down! - Hey, what?
肯尼
Kenny!
虎爪
Twisting tiger.
你哪里学来的
Where did you learn that?
程师父教我的
- 北京的程师父 - 不是 克伦萧区的弗莱迪程教我的
他们是兄弟
They're brothers.
好极了
Oh, all right, all right.
为什么你会和711一起
711？
711?
他永远都不知道闭嘴
嘿 我听懂了
Hey! I heard that. I heard that.
别说我坏话
Don't be talking about me, man.
你们来查伪钞的吗？
You are here about some funny money.
你怎么知道
How you know?
- 一百元的伪钞吧 - 对 这里有人用伪钞吗
- Cnotes, right? - Yeah. Any of them came through here?
有个熟客
One of my regulars came in here a few days ago…
几天前输了五万元
dropped about 50 large on the tables in there.
我正要找兄弟们去找他算账
I was about to go down there with my boys and tune his ass up.
但他第二天来了 还清了全额
But he comes in the next day with the whole thing.
全是顺号码的百元新钞
Brandnew 100dollar bills, sequential.
我猜是假的 因为他 只是领一般薪水而已
I figure they're fake because this guy's got a regular day job.
我验过那些钞票 是真的
So I test them, and they checked out.
钞票还在吗？
You still have the bills?
还剩下一些
Still got my lunch money from the third grade.
给我看看
Let me see them.
你干什么
Hold it. What are you doing?
是假的
Oh, it's fake.
他骗了你
He got you.
你说是谁给你的
Who you say gave that to you?
他叫小京 在瑞恩广场工作
Cat named Zing. Work down at Reign Plaza.
在我找到他前 你们最好找到他
Tell you what, you better hope you find him before I do.
好吧
All right.
对不起 洛杉矶警察
Excuse me. L.A.P.D.
我们想找个叫小京的人
We're looking for a guy named Zing.
你给我站住 回来 快回来
You! Come here! Come back here!
你这个混蛋回来
Hey! Hey! You little rascal!
立刻给我滚回来
Get back here!
立刻回来
Get back here right now!
原来是鼎鼎有名的李督察
告诉你 干掉你 江湖上我就更有名了
其实 我都不知道我来干嘛
Heh. You know what? I don't even know why the hell I'm here.
我又不是中国人
I ain't even Chinese.
好吧 对不起
All right, I'm sorry.
我想有人想先跟他们谈谈
I think there's someone who would like to talk to them first.
干嘛这么暴力 有必要吗？
What'd you do that for? Unnecessary!
把我的补牙踢崩了 你要赔
You done knocked out my filling, girl. That's gonna cost you.
我从没打过女人 是你逼我的
I ain't never hit a woman, but your ass is pushing it!
好啦 好啦
Okay, all right, all right.
我走就是了
I'll go.
你给我等着瞧
Better watch your back.
李
Lee.
Lee!
发生了什么事
What happened?
那个叫伊莎贝拉的女人把你打晕了 她耍了你
That lady Isabella knock you out, that's what happened. She played you.
- 没有 - 是真的
- No. - Yes, she did.
- 她救了我们的命 - 什么
- She save our life. - What?
- 否则我们已被胡莉杀了 - 你疯了吗
- Hu Li could have killed us. - Lee, are you crazy, man?
看看我们 跟死有什么两样
Look at us. We good as dead!
卡特 别再唧唧歪歪了
Stop your whining, Carter!
我就要唧唧歪歪 怎样 我一巴掌扇得你满眼冒金星
What you gonna do if I don't stop, huh? I will slap the hell out of you right now.
- 是吗 - 是啊
- Yeah? - Yeah.
- 我一个大嘴巴把你抽回非洲 - 是吗
- I'll bitchslap you back to Africa! - Oh, you will?
来吧 我倒想见识见识
Yeah. Come on, let me see that.
- 给我见识见识啊 - 来啊 是吗
- I wanna see you do that! - Come on. Yeah?
老虎的屁股你都敢摸
You don't know who you're messing with!
鳄鱼的牙你都敢拔 是吧
You don't know who you're messing with.
- 等我把你鼻子咬掉 - 你咬
- I'll bite your damn nose off, man. - You bite.
- 好啊 - 来吧
- Yeah. - Come on!
我不信任她
把她留在这儿是个错误
上面有命令 现在不能动她
我想把她可爱的小嘴唇儿 从她脸上切下去
然后跟那两个蠢警察一起 埋在沙漠里
吃苹果吗？
Some apple?
把那把刀拿开 贱货 别搞出意外
I'd put that knife away, bitch, before you have an accident.
没有用的
Ain't no use, man.
告诉我三合会会怎么杀我们
Just tell me how the Triads are gonna kill us.
他们会折磨我们三日
They will torture us for three days.
- 这我撑得住 - 然后让我们断子绝孙
- I can handle that. - Then they'll cut off our egg rolls.
断子绝孙
Cutoff our egg rolls?
不 我们快逃
Hell, no! Let's get the hell out of here!
加油 老兄 别放弃
Come on, man! Don't give up!
- 我不想死 - 别吵
- I don't wanna die! - Be quiet.
- 把左腿给我 - 干什么
- Okay, give me your left leg. - What for?
左腿
Left leg! Aah!
像这样
Like this.
- 站稳 - 好
- Hold tight. - Okay.
对 咬它
That's it. Bite that thing.
咬它像猴子一样咬它
Bite it! Bite it like a little monkey!
用力咬对 使劲儿
Go on, bite it! There you go.
用力 用你的虎牙
Yank it! Use them tiger teeth!
扯呀 差不多了 对
Yeah! Grab it, pull on it! You almost got it, that's it.
该死
Oh, shit!
搞什么
What the hell? Wow.
帮我松绑 快
Lee, untie me. Hurry up, man!
这些人像里全是钱
All these statues full of money.
你好啊 班杰明
Hello, Benjamin!
- 你在干什么 - 我在搜集证据
- What are you doing? - I'm taking this for evidence.
卡特
Carter.
- 感觉到了吗？- 对 我们慢下来了
- You feel that? - Yeah, we slowing down, man.
- 发生了什么事 - 我来告诉你吧
- What happened? - I'll tell you what happened.
李 快来
Come on, Lee!
卡特 上去
Carter, go up.
卡特
Carter! Carter!
- 卡特 - 李
- Carter! - Lee!
- 发生什么事 - 你丢下我
- What happened? - You left me.
我没有 我在车顶等你
I didn't leave you, man. I was waiting up there for you.
老兄 我才不下去
Whoa, man! I ain't going in there!
- 快点儿 - 那里有老鼠
- Come on! - There's rats in there!
- 没有老鼠 - 看那只老鼠
- There's no rats! - Look at that rat!
拉斯维加斯
Las Vegas?
赌城 我们来这里干嘛
Vegas? What the hell we doing in Vegas?
看 赤龙
Look. Red Dragon.
那是谭瑞奇游艇的名字
That's the name of Ricky Tan's boat.
李
Lee.
那是洗一亿元黑钱的方法
That's how you launder a hundred million dollars in cash.
- 走吧 - 走吧
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- 对不起 - 该死
- Sorry. - Damn!
一个一个来嘛 你有什么毛病
One at a time. What the hell is wrong with you?
（赤龙赌场）
- 等等 - 什么
- Wait a second, man. - What?
- 我们不能这样子进去 - 为什么
- We can't go in there like this. - Why?
- 我们要「潮」一点 - 什么「潮」
- We gotta look fly. - What you mean fly?
在赌城人靠衣装 我们不能就这么进去
Mack out. We can't go in there like this.
什么 衣装
What does it mean, mack out?
跟我来吧 亚洲兄弟 我带你去
Follow me, my Asian brother. I'll show you.
来吧
Come on. Come on.
好了 我们就是来这里
That's where we're going, right there.
进去后 你跟我站开一点
When we get there, you stay a couple steps behind.
你有点臭味
Huh? You smell funky.
你踩到老鼠屎了
I think you stepped in some rat shit.
这以前是牛仔帽 现在是太阳帽
It was a cowboy hat, and now it's a pith helmet, and once.
等等 我回头再跟你谈
Hold up. I'll talk to you in a bit.
两位 有什么可效劳
Hi. Can I help you gentlemen?
黑西装 裤长42
Yeah. I'm gonna need black, 42 long…
我除了真丝什么也不穿
and nothing touches this body but pure silk.
帮我搭档在童装部找套衣服吧
Get my partner something from the Kids Department.
你那位搭档也要穿真丝吗？
Would your partner like to be wrapped in silk as well?
有人认为很老套
Some people think it's tacky…
但我喜欢恋人穿情侣装
but I really enjoy it when couples dress alike.
我们不是恋人
No, this ain't no couple thing, man.
我们是警察 在查危险的案件 需要乔装
We're police officers. We're working a case, and we need clothes.
很多人追我们
Yes. There are a lot of men chasing us.
他们当然会追你们 不用担心
As well they should be. Listen, you have nothing to worry about, okay?
我会把你俩变成全场的焦点
I'm gonna turn you two into the belle of the ball.
- 谢谢 - 别客气
- Thank you. - Absolutely.
你先来吧 好吗？
Let's start with you, shall we?
你有咖啡色的面孔 皮肤很好
You've got the mochaccino face, wonderful skin…
宽阔的肩膀 就放只死动物在你身上吧
and the big, broad shoulders. Let's put a dead animal on you.
鳄鱼皮 奶油色
Croc skin. Butter cream, butter cream, croc skin, butter cream.
腰围几寸我们进去吧
What size is the waist? Let's go in.
- 我想… - 嘿
- I wanna… - Hey!
别乱碰我 甜心
Watch it, sweetness.
- 他很火爆啊 - 蜜糖杯
- He's got fire to him. - Honey cups!
- 我喜欢 - 去拿衣服吧
- I like that. - Go get the clothes! Hurry up!
我去找几件出来 天啊
I'll pull some items. Ooh, Jesus.
好有性格 我很快就回来
Ha, ha. Lil Kim, I'll be back.
- 你有看到吗？- 他喜欢你
- You see that? - He likes you.
我不会再和你一起购物了
I'm not shopping with you no more.
（开张大吉）
装作你很有钱的样子
Act like you're rich.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen…
史蒂芬瑞恩 赤龙赌场的所有者及创办人
Steven Reign, owner and founder of the Red Dragon casino.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢 大家晚安
Thank you. Good evening.
一千年前 中国有个富庶的小村
A thousand years ago, a small, wealthy village in China…
村民们请了一条龙看守山洞的宝藏
hired a young dragon to guard their treasures in a cave.
村民给它送去很多食物
The people of the village started sneaking him extra food…
希望它越来越强壮
hoping to make him stronger.
龙后来长得太肥大了 塞在洞口
The dragon grew so big he got stuck…
宝藏此永远藏在它后面了
and the treasure was trapped behind him for all eternity.
女士们先生们 我找到了 那失踪的宝藏
Ladies and gentlemen, I have found that lost treasure.
它就在这间世界上最大的赌场中
It is here, inside the greatest casino in the world!
欢迎来赤龙
Welcome to the Red Dragon…
这里人人都是赢家
where everybody is a winner!
黑 29
Black, 29.
这里是世界最大的洗钱场所
Look at this place, Lee. It's the biggest front in the world.
你说得对
Yeah, right.
你好 喝点什么吗？
Hello. drink?
- 抽烟吗？- 要喝点什么吗？
- Cigarettes? - Drink?
抱着我
Put your arms around me.
- 什么 - 抱紧我
- What? - Hold me close.
这里到处是摄像头
There are cameras everywhere.
- 怎么了 - 我可能遇到麻烦了
- What's going on? - I think I may be in trouble, Lee.
我真的需要你帮忙
I really need your help.
上次你要帮忙 我醒来发现自己就在货车上
Last time you needed my help, I woke up in a truck.
我是卧底 我没选择
I'm undercover, Lee. I had no choice.
你得信任我
And you have to trust me.
看我右后方
Look over my right shoulder.
那是数钞票的房间
That's the soft count room.
我们猜印版就在里面
We think the plates are in there.
我要你去拿回来
I need you to go and get them.
为什么你不去
Why don't you go get them?
因为我若猜错
Because if I'm wrong…
身份就会被揭穿
then my entire cover is blown, understand?
我怎知道可以信任你
How do I know I can trust you?
揽我入怀
Dip me.
我现在认真地请求你
I'm asking for real now.
可以帮特勤局一个忙吗？
Will you help the Secret Service?
李
Hey, Lee. Lee!
你干什么
What are you doing?
谢谢 给你
Thank you, man. Take this.
跳舞
Dancing.
Dancing?
我来这里工作 出生入死
I'm up here working, putting my life on the line…
你却跟无脑美女跳舞
and you're up here messing around, dancing with some bimbo?
她有带朋友来吗？
Does she have a friend?
那是伊莎贝拉
That was Isabella.
她说印版在数钞室
Says the plates are in the soft count room.
李 你不是说伊莎贝拉吧 你疯了吗？
Lee, I know you didn't just say Isabella. Are you crazy, man?
- 那女人又来陷害你了 - 不是的
- That girl is setting you up again. - No.
- 不 我要去看看 - 不 等等
- I'm gonna find out. - No, wait, man.
到处是保安 你要声东击西
There's security all over. If you're gonna do this, you need a distraction.
我去引开注意 你伺机行事
So keep your eye on me, you'll know when to make your move.
- 好 - 去吧
- Good. - Cool.
快啊 掷骰子吧 大老爹
Come on, roll them, big daddy!
加油 德州佬
Come on, Tex! Come on, Tex!
嘿 真厉害
Hey, hey, hey! Good roll, man!
这张桌子很旺啊
This table's hot!
我也想赢点钱 我加入
I want some of this money. Get me in this game. Come on.
你留意到今晚最少要换 五万元筹码吧
Sir, uh, are you aware that there's a $50, 000 buyin this evening?
那么给我十万元筹码
If that's the case, give me $100, 000 in chips.
我要健怡百事可乐和辣鸡翅
Let me have a diet Pepsi and some hot wings.
- 给他筹码 - 我们来玩吧
- Give him the chips. - Let's play!
我要赢点钱 等一下 每个筹码多少
Whoo! I'm gonna get some of this. Whoa, whoa, whoa. What's this?
五百元 先生
Fivehundreddollar chips, sir.
因为我是黑人 你就给我五百元的筹码吗？
You gave me 500dollar chips because I'm black?
不 先生 我只是以为
Uh, no, sir, I did not. I just assumed that.
你以为黑人兄弟
Assumed a brother coming in here…
只玩得起五百元的筹码吗？
can only afford $500 a roll. Is that it?
不 我完全没那个意思
Uh, no, I didn't think that at all, sir.
- 你种族歧视吗？- 不 我不是
- You a racist? - No, I'm not, sir.
那为什么人人都有一千元的筹码
How come everybody else got thousanddollar chips…
- 只有黑人的是五百元的 - 我不知道
- black man got a nickel? - I don't know.
怎么会这样
How did that happen?
- 就这么 - 就这么发生了是吧
- It just… - It just happened.
真是太过份了 你以为我们受了362年奴役
Ah, this is crazy. You think my people suffered 362 years of slavery…
你就可以给我五百元筹码 让我回去种棉花吗？
so you could send us back to the cotton fields with 500dollar chips?
- 不是的 - 我像黑奴乔治吗
- No. - Do I look like Chicken George?
- 不像 - 那你是怎么回事
- You do not. - What is that?
先生 我觉得你该冷静一点
Sir, I think you should calm down.
我觉得你应该哪儿凉快哪儿待着去
You should go over there and count something.
- 把筹码给我 我要一千元的 - 等我一下
- I want thousanddollar chips! - Give me a second.
快 我只想要被公平对待 这样的要求过份吗？
I just wanna be treated fairly. Is that too much to ask?
- 不过分 - 这样的要求过份吗？
- No. - Is that too much to ask?
- 不 - 真不知道发生了什么事
- No. - Who knows what going on?
九号桌有麻烦
I got a problem on table 9.
怎么没黑人表演 黑人不够好吗？
How come ain't no black people performing? We ain't good enough?
莱诺李奇今晚演出
We got Lionel Richie performing here tonight.
他自从担任「海军准将」主唱 之后就不是黑人了
Lionel ain't been black since the Commodores, man.
「桃子和草」、「葛蕾蒂丝奈特与种子合唱团」呢
What about Peaches and Herb? Gladys Knight and the Pips?
「艾克和蒂娜」呢
Ike and Tina.
他们可以复合呀 太疯狂了
They can get back together. This is crazy.
先生 何不冷静一下 赢点钱尽兴一下
Why don't you calm down, win some money and have fun?
冷什么静 我讨厌你老叫我冷静
I ain't calming down! I'm sick of you trying to calm me down!
有麻烦 上
We got a problem. Go.
我有个梦想
I have a dream…
希望白人和黑人
that white people and black people…
甚至中国人
and even Chinese people…
可以在同桌赌钱 用筹码一样
can gamble together without getting different chips!
看在兄弟份上
Hold it, hold it. In the spirit of brotherhood…
我们掷骰子吧 来吧
let's just play craps, man. Come on, let's go. Come on, come on.
糟了
Oh, shit.
嘿
Hey.
抓住他
Get him!
别跑
Stop!
李督察 这是颗樱桃炸弹
如果你不听话的话
只要我轻轻一按
32颗顽皮的牙就会蹦进你的脑袋
六点是赢家 太棒了
Winner, 6. Yes!
太棒了
Yes, yes, yes!
感觉很棒 刚才谁摸我屁股
I feel good. Oh, who put their hand on my butt?
再来把 把骰子给我 我赢了多少
Do it again. Give me that, give me that. How much I win?
二十万 先生
Two hundred thousand, sir.
二十万元
Two hundred thousand dollars?
好棒 好吧
Yeah! Whoo! All right.
掷吧 我要掷七点
Coming out. This seven I'm about to roll…
是为曼德拉坐的27年冤狱而掷的
is for the 27 years Mandela spent in that prison, couldn't get no justice…
他吃尽苦头 所以我不会掷输
and took all that crap. I ain't gonna crap out.
不会输的
No!
这是为曼德拉而掷的
This one is for Mandela!
七点 七点赢
A winner, seven.
终获自由 终获自由
Free at last. Free at last.
终获自由
Free at last.
都出去
Out.
试想像有一种生意
Imagine a business…
人人都给你钱
where people hand you money…
你给他们的回报 却完全是零
and you hand them back absolutely nothing.
这就是真正的美国梦
Now, that's the real American dream.
托几片金属的福
Thanks to a few pieces of metal…
加上美国最漂亮的海关人员
and a most beautiful U.S. customs agent…
我东山复出了
I'm back in business.
李 看看你
Look at you, Lee.
你的样子真是糟透了
You look ridiculous.
你知道你本来没必要落得如此下场的
You know it didn't have to be like this.
真遗憾
It's too bad.
有其父必有其子
Like father, like son.
老板 他去顶楼了
看看这个老笨蛋
Look at this old fool.
他以为自己在干嘛
What does he think he's doing?
要找一个可靠而忠心的搭档
I tell you, it's almost impossible to find a partner…
几乎是不可能的 李 同意吗？
that is trustworthy and loyal. Don't you agree, Lee?
停止下注 所有人都别碰这桌子
Everything stays on the table. Don't nobody touch that table.
好吧
All right.
赢家四点
Winner, four high, four high.
太棒了
Yes! Yes!
那是五十万元
Oh, my goodness! That's $500, 000!
- 五十万 - 下来 先生
- Yes! That's $500, 000! - Come on, sir.
告诉他们拿下李的伙伴
- 给我换现金 - 请先下来
- Cash me out. - You're gonna have to get off the table.
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
搭档的问题是 他们会死
The trouble with partners is they die.
你也一样
玩开心点
Have fun.
再过几分钟
你会主动求我按这个
别动 美国特勤局
Don't move! U.S. Secret Service!
你们被捕了
You're under arrest.
他们会护送你去出纳部
These gentlemen will escort you to the cashier.
好 以免有钱白人拦途截劫 走吧
Good. I don't wanna getjumped by any of these rich white folks. Let's go.
谢谢你们 安全第一
I appreciate this, fellas. You never can be too safe.
什么鬼
What the?
- 不好意思 痛吗？- 你 站住
- I'm sorry, man. Did that hurt? - Hey! you! Hold it!
你没事吧 你还好吗？
Hey. You okay? You all right?
黑人赢大钱你们就眼红了
Black man on a roll, y'all start tripping.
你们都后退 冷静点
Y'all get back! Just calm down!
我说了 后退 后退
I said back! Get back! Get back! Get back!
嘿 住手下来
Ow! Hey, stop! Get down!
冷静点 放松 把棍子放下
Easy. Drop the stick.
李
Lee! Aah!
李 你去了哪儿我赢了大钱啊
Where you been, Lee? I've been on a roll, man!
你发生了什么事
What happened to you, man?
你口里的光是什么
What's that light?
老兄 大事不妙
Aw, man, this can't be good.
让开 别挡路 好吗
Move! Would you get out of my way?
你怎么了
What's wrong with you?
你发生了什么事
What happened to you, man?
该死
Damn!
你干嘛不跟我说口里有炸弹
Why didn't tell me you had a bomb in your mouth?
- 我说了 - 不 你没说
- I did! - No, you didn't!
- 我这么说的 - 这是啥意思
- I said "mm"! - What the hell is "mm"?
谭瑞奇没有死 我们得去顶楼
Ricky Tan's still alive. We have to get to the penthouse.
谭瑞奇已经死了
Ricky Tan dead.
你胡说什么
What you talking about? Whoa!
你去找瑞奇 我来对付她
Lee. Go after Ricky, man. I got this.
- 卡特 - 去吧 这里我搞得定
- Carter. - Just go, man. I got this.
这次我不会因为你是女人手下留情
I'm not gonna hold back this time just because you're a woman.
我会当你是男人
I'm gonna pretend you're a man.
一个身材完美的俊男
A very beautiful man with a perfect body…
我会约他看电影的
who I'd like to take to the movies.
这一招不懂吧 埃及拳
You don't know nothing about this? Egyptian style, girl.
想试试这个吗 来吧
You want some of this? Come on.
放马过来
Whoo, ah! Bring it on!
- 你没事吧 - 我没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
你得去医院
You need help.
我之前不知道你到底是哪方的
I didn't know which side you were on.
现在你知道了
Well, now you know.
你到底有什么毛病
What's wrong with you, woman?
你好香啊
Mm, you smell good.
谢谢你 班杰明 谢谢
Thank you, Benjamin. Thank you.
我们俩本是天生一对
We could have been a good couple.
可以产生些浪漫的火花
We could have had something special.
可惜你是个疯婆子
But you one crazyass bitch!
美国人真爱赌博 对吗 瑞恩先生
Americans love to gamble, don't they, Mr. Reign?
我从不赌博
I never gamble.
我要提早结束我俩的交易
Oh, I'm, uh, cutting our deal short.
- 那我的印版呢 - 印版归我
- And my plates? - The plates stay with me.
相信你不会反对吧
I'm sure you won't have a problem with that.
我很喜欢你那个龙和宝藏的故事
I enjoyed that little story you told about the dragon and the treasure.
我妈妈以前常跟我说那故事
My mother used to tell it to me all the time.
你知道那故事的寓意吗
Do you know the moral of that story?
贪得无厌没好下场
Greed will imprison us all.
我讨厌迷信的胡说八道
I hate that fortunecookie shit.
就像你爸爸一样
Just like your father.
我本来真的想帮他
I really did try to help him, you know.
跟他分赃
To share with him.
让你生活过得好一点
To make your life better.
可惜他太软弱了
But he was too weak.
太害怕转变
Too afraid of change.
把印版给我 都结束了
Give me the plates. It's over.
我不相信
I don't think it's over.
这国家到处都是赌场
There are casinos all over this country.
李 我可以让你飞黄腾达
I can make you a very rich man, Lee.
不要重蹈你爸爸的覆辙
Don't make the same mistake your father did.
如果你碰那枪的话 我便会杀了你
If you reach for that gun, I'll kill you.
你不记得吗 我已经死了
Don't you remember? I'm already dead.
瑞奇 你好吗
Hey, Ricky. How you doing?
李 你似乎已经控制大局了 我得去楼下 天啊
I see you got everything under control. I'm gonna go downstairs Goddamn!
瑞恩怎么了
What happened to Reign?
想知道你爸爸是怎样死的吗
Would you like me to tell you how your father died?
等等 李
Hey, hey. Wait one second, Lee.
不值得杀他 他想让你中圈套
It ain't worth it, man. He trying to trick you.
别太过份
Don't go too far, now.
他从不会贪生怕死 也不肯同流合污
He never begged for his life or tried to make a deal.
- 把枪放下 - 我开枪前那片刻
- Put the gun down. - All he asked me…
他只是恳求我
just seconds before I pulled the trigger…
答应他不杀你
was that I promise not to kill you.
真是太可悲了
Oh, it was so pathetic.
该死 他太过份了 开枪吧 蹦死他
Oh, hell, no. He don't went too far. Shoot his ass now, Lee. Shoot his ass!
你打算怎样
What are you gonna do, Lee?
你只要按下扳机 然后：
All you gotta do is pull that trigger back and bam!
你打算余生像你爸爸一样躲藏吗？
Are you going to spend the rest of your life hiding like your father?
别让他那样说你爸爸 开枪
Don't let him talk about your daddy like that. Shoot!
你做不到吧
You can't do it, can you?
你做得到的 这里只有我们
Yes, hell, you can. Ain't nobody up here but us.
- 杀死他吧… - 正如我所料
- Go off on him. - Just as I thought.
他用的是激将法 开枪
He trying to punk you. Shoot him!
快点 不开枪也揍扁他啊
Come on! If you ain't, kung fu his ass!
卡特
Carter! Ah!
不
No!
该死
Damn!
李 好脚法
Good kick, Lee.
那是意外
It was an accident.
没问题 我们说他想坐车就好啦
That's okay. We'll say he tried to catch a cab.
你手中的是 该死的 不
What's that in your? Aw, hell, no.
女士 听我说 快放下那炸弹 关掉它
Lady, listen to me. Put that bomb down and turn it off!
- 卡特 我们得跳出去 - 你疯了 我才不跳
- Carter, we have to jump! - You crazy, man. I ain'tjumping.
用你的外套吧 关掉炸弹
Use your jacket! Hey, turn that bomb off! Aah!
真是个疯子
Crazyass!
还不错嘛
That wasn't so bad.
我真不敢相信我飞了一万英里 就为了来搅这滩浑水
I cannot believe I flew 10, 000 miles for this shit.
李探员 我不想承认 不过
Detective Lee, I hate to admit it…
美国特勤局真的很感激你
but the United States Secret Service is indebted to you.
- 谢谢你 - 谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
飞机上见
I'll see you on board. Mmhm.
我也想多谢你
I wanna thank you too.
跟你合作很愉快
It was nice working with you.
我看到了
I saw that.
你这狡猾的王八蛋 她吻了你吧
You sly devil, you. She kissed you, didn't she?
你也很酷啊 头也不回 我喜欢
Ah, you played it cool too. Walking away, not looking back. I like that.
对 我是老手
Yeah. I'm a player.
- 她飞去哪儿 - 她去纽约
- Where is she headed? - She's going to New York.
- 你的登机门在那边 - 对
- Is that your gate down there? - Yep.
我的登机门在这边
Well, I'm this way.
- 那表示我们得说再见了 - 大概是
- Guess that mean goodbye. - I guess so.
谢谢你 卡特
Thank you, Carter.
自己多保重 李
Take good care of yourself, Lee.
- 噢 卡特 - 怎么了 李
- Oh, Carter. - Yeah, Lee?
什么事
What's up?
我有个东西想给你
There is something I want you to have.
这是你爸爸的警徽 我不能要
No, man. This is your daddy's badge. I can't take that, man.
没关系 我终于可以放下了
It's okay. No. Finally, I can let it go.
谢谢你
Thank you, man.
知道吗 我也有个东西给你
Hey, you know what? I got something for you too.
这是什么
What is this?
一万美金
That's $10, 000, man.
我今早在凯撒赌场赢的 我的手气仍然很旺
Got it at the tables this morning at Caesars. I'm still hot.
- 我不能要 - 别担心 我还有很多
- I can't take this. - Don't worry about it. I got a lot more.
- 不 - 拿去 好好享受一下
- No, no, no. - Go ahead. Enjoy yourself.
我不能要它
No, Carter. I can't have this.
暂时放下警察的包袱去享乐一下吧
Would you stop acting like a cop for one second, man, and live it up?
一定有你想要的东西
There gotta be something you want. Come on.
想一想吧
Think about it.
飞往纽约的
Final boarding call for flight 44…
44号班机的乘客 请尽快到登机门
to New York City's LaGuardia. All ticketed passengers should now…
我一直想去麦迪逊广场花园
I always wanted to go to Madison Square Garden…
看纽约尼克斯队的篮球赛
see the Knicks play.
- 纽约市 - 头等舱
- New York City? - First class.
- 广场酒店 - 也许来点木须肉
- The Plaza Hotel? - Maybe a little mu shu?
最好不过
Amen to that, brother.
- 那么 你意下如何 - 你知道吗
- So, what do you say? - You know what, man?
我完全可以再休一次假
I can use another vacation.
打板
Mark.
- 开拍 - 走吧
- Action! - Let's go!
好的 拿好
All right, take that.
- 你没事吧 - 他没事吧
- You all right? - Is he okay?
成龙没事吧 成龙总是没事的
Jackie okay? Jackie always okay.
- 这是犹太餐吗？- 是的 先生
- Is this the kosher meal? - Yes, that's our kosher meal.
- 这叫什么名字 - 鱼丸冻
- What's the name of it? - Gefilte fish.
- 鱼丸冻 - 鱼丸冻
- Gefilte fish. - Gefilte fish.
熏鲑鱼贝果 我最喜欢的
Lox and bagels. It's my favorite.
- 这东西叫什么名字 - 鱼丸冻
- What's the name of this stuff? - Gefilte fish.
鱼冻丸
Gefilke fishOh.
- 这鱼叫什么名字 - 鱼丸冻
- What's the name? - Gefilte fish.
鱼冻丸 鱼丸冻
Gefilke fiGefilta.
你知道这是什么吗 是什么
You know what this is? What is it?
- 鱼冻丸 - 是鱼丸
- Gefilte fish. - It's filte fish.
鱼丸 你想吃我的鱼丸吗？
Filte fish. Want some of my filte fish?
你想吃我的什么丸来着
You want any of this sh? Uh, what's the name of the fish?
鱼丸冻
Gefilte fish.
鱼丸冻啊
鱼丸冻 对不起
Gefilte fish. All right, I'm sorry.
- 鱼丸冻 我喜欢 - 我才不喜欢
- Gefilte. I love this stuff. - I really don't.
所有的黑人都吃这个 谁会吃熏鲑鱼贝果
Black people all over eating this. Who eats lox and bagels?
我可以吃鱼丸冻吗？
Can I have some gilte fish?
小姐 成龙 踢门
Lady! Jackie, kick.
好的 克里斯塔克
Okay, Chris Tucker.
成龙 踢门
Jackie, kick it.
又叫成龙
Jackie again?
我们倒想见识见识 成龙
We'd love to see that. Won't we love to see that, Jackie.
成龙 我们倒想见识见识
Jackie, we'd like to see that.
Jackie, we would love to see that. Wouldn't we?
- 他的名字是李 该死的 - 李 我们得见识见识
- His name is Lee, goddamn it! - Lee, we would love to see that.
我们倒想见识见识 是吗
Wouldn't we, Lee?
- 一定有你想要的 - 我一直想去广场麦迪逊
- Gotta be something you want. - I always want to go to SquareMadi.
我一直想去广场
I always want to go to SquareShh.
我一直梦想去广场麦顿
I always dream to Square Margon.
我一直想去
I always want to go to.
现在我不能集中了
Now I'm gone.
我很紧张 每次说到「花园」就紧张
Now I'm nervous. Every "garden", I'm nervous.
- 麦迪逊广场花园 - 对
- Madison Square Garden. - Yes.
我一直想去广麦迪逊
I always want to go to the SqMadison.
很多人追我们
A lot of men chasing us.
他们当然会追 你这么英俊
Because you're a very goodlooking man.
如果我没女友也会追你
If I didn't have a girlfriend, I'd take run at you.
我会放你在浴缸 给你水泡 拍你屁股
Put you in a bubble bath, put water wings on you, spank your little bottom.
但听着 我们现在要这样
Listen, here's what we.
镇定点 你笑我
Easy, easy. Look it. You're giggling at me.
小心我带你回家罚你
I'll take you home and just punish you.
你们两个我都要
I need both of you.
你这狡猾的混蛋 她吻了你吧
You sly devil, you. She kissed you, didn't she?
我喜欢
Yeah. I like that.
等等 谁打来的
OhHold on Who's calling?
- 跟你老爸打个招呼吧 - 喂
- Say hello to your dad. - Hello?
喂 是的
Hello? Yeah.
我在拍戏 七点钟再打来
I'm filming, man. IS Call me back at 7:00.
我在拍戏 瞪着成龙 再打来吧
I'm looking Jackie Chan dead in his eyes.
我们在镜头上 再打给我
We're on the Call me back.
- 回头再打给我 - 你也太不专业了
- Call me back. - Are you a professional?
- 我们可是在拍戏啊 你还开着手机 - 不 你不能跟成龙说话 不行
- We are filming, you turn on your phone? - No, you can't speak to Jackie Chan.
不行 他们想跟你说话
No. They wanna speak to you.
- 喂 - 非常抱歉
- Hello? - I'm sorry about this.
我们在拍戏
We are filming right now.
你还不好意思呢 你在浪费我们的底片
You sorry? You waste our film.
晚点打来吧 七点钟
Call me back later, 7:00.
可恶
Damn!
他不会在《尖峰时刻3》出现了
He ain't gonna be in Rush Hour 3.